Guide to the ARS Audiotape Collection ARS.0070
Archive of Recorded Sound
- 40. Miscellaneous items
  - audiocassettes
    - Great Pacific Jazz Band, Golden Eagle Jazz Band with Chris Norris (vocal), Pismo Beach, October 1983., 1983-10; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 16)
      Norris, Chris; Great Pacific Jazz Band; Golden Eagle Jazz Band
    - Zimbalist. Impressions, Three Songs; Kabalevsky. Cello Concerto No 1, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 16)
      Details
      Zimbalist Sr.: Impressions Jorge Bolet, piano.
      Zimbalist Sr.: Three Songs of Edna St. Vincent Millay 1- Rain Come Down 2- Mariposa 3- One-Two-Three Ilona Kombrink, soprano Vladimir Sokoloff, piano
      Kabalevsky: Cello Concerto No. 1 Yo-Yo Ma, cello Cleveland Orchestra Leonard Slatkin, conductor
      Slatkin, Leonard; Bolet, Jorge; Sokoloff, Vladimir; Zimbalist, Efrem, Sr.; Ma, Yo-Yo; Kombrink, Ilona; Kabalevsky, Dmitry Borisovich; Cleveland Orchestra
    - D'Indy. Trio; Malipiero. Violin Concerto, Piano Concerto No 5, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 16)
      Listings
      D'Indy: Trio for Clarinet, Cello, and Piano Rose, Adams, Cosgrove
      Malipiero: Violin concerto (1932) 1- Allegro 2- Lento 3- Allegro Andre Gertler, violin Turin Radio Orchestra Fernando Previtali, conductor
      Malipiero: Piano Concerto No 5 (1958) Gino Gorini, piano Turin Radio Orchestra Rossi, conductor
      Previtali, Fernando; D'Indy, Vincent; Malipiero, Gian Francesco; Turin Radio Television Orchestra; Gertler, Andre; Gorini, Gino
    - Shchedrin. Piano Concerto No 2; Vaughan-Williams. Five Mystical Songs; Strohl. Music of the Sea, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 16)
      Shchedrin: Piano Concerto No 2 Rodion Shchedrin, piano
      Vaughan-Williams: Five Mystical Songs (1911) Willcocks/English Chamber Orchestra
      Strohl, Rita: Music of the Sea Bergstoff, piano
      English Chamber Orchestra; Shchedrin, Rodion; Strohl, Rita; Vaughan-Williams, Ralph
    - Harris. String Quartet No 3; Concerto for Piano, Clarinet and String Quartet; Gretchaninoff. Choral Songs; Hanson. Pan and Priest; Saint-Saens. Cello Sonata No 2, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 16)
      Harris: String Quartet No 3 Arriaga String Quartet
      Harris: Concerto for Piano, Clarinet and String Quartet J. Harris, piano Susika, clarinet Arriaga String Quartet
      Gretchaninov: Choral Songs 1- Dawn 2- Over an Inaccessable Height 3- Snowdrops 4- Snowflakes 5- Lullaby Leningrad Radio Symphony Chorus Sanderling, conductor
      Hanson: Pan and Priest World Youth Orchestra Howard Hanson, conductor
      Saint-Saens: Cello Sonata No 2 Op 123
      Last Move?
      Leningrad Radio Symphony Chorus; Harris, Roy, 1898-1979; World Youth Symphony Orchestra; Saint-Saens, Camille; Arriaga String Quartet; Gretchaninov, Alexander; Hanson, Howard
    - Fenstermaker plays Bach. Grace Cathedral, San Francisco., 1986-08-10; 1 audiocassette(s) folders (Box 17)
      Toccata in F major, BWV 540 Sonata I in E flat, BWV 525 Prelude and Fugue in A minor, BWV 543 Toccata, Adagio, and Fugue in C, BWV 564 Three Chorales from the 'Neumeister' Collection Prelude and Fugue in C major, BWV 547 Toccata and Fugue in D minor, BWV 565
      Fenstermaker, John, Dr.; Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750
    - SIM* ARS NOVA - Digital. Dreistimmige Tonsatze altfranz. Meister in Computer-Realisationen, 1 audiocassette(s) folders; Audible MIDI recordings made in 1988 or earlier at the SSPK in Berlin by Norbert Böker-Heil, a scholar of trecento music but also a deft hand at computers. Böker-Heil has been retired since about 1990. He published an edition of trecento music (computer typeset) in that era; it was a collaborative project. He also did a lot of work of RISM. (Box 17)
      Selfridge-Field, Eleanor
    - Minneapolis Auditorium Organ, In Concert, Program 1. Organists Dr. Edward Berryman and Robert Vickery. Works by Bach, Berryman, Wagner, Ravel, Sibelius, Faure, and Mulet., 1986-10-24; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 17)
    - Minneapolis Auditorium Organ, Tom Hazelton in Concert, Program III. Works by Bach, Clarke, Ireland, Purvis, and Hazelton., 1987-06-26; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 17)
    - Paul Kling, violin. Beethoven Violin Concerto. Mozart Violin Concerto, K 219. NHK Symphony; Aeschbacher; Karajan [2 copies], 1954-1955 (Box 17)
      Beethoven, Ludwig van. Concertos, violin, orchestra, op. 61, D major. Paul Kling, violin. NHK Symphony. Niklaus Aeschbacher, conductor. 1955.
      Mozart, Wolfgang Amadeus. Concertos, violin, orchestra, K. 219, A major. Paul Kling, violin. NHK Symphony. Herbert Von Karajan, conductor. 1954.
      Kling, Paul; Barber, Charles; NHK Kōkyō Gakudan; Aeschbacher, Niklaus, 1917-1995; Karajan, Herbert von; Beethoven, Ludwig van, 1770-1827; Mozart, Wolfgang Amadeus, 1756-1791